Register of the Richard Thomas Kennedy papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Richard Thomas Kennedy papers
1974-2017
83063
Hoover Institution Archives
92 manuscript boxes, 2 envelopes, 17 phonotapes, 2 video tapes (39.0 linear feet)
Speeches, correspondence, memoranda, reports, transcripts of hearings, and printed matter relating to nuclear power plants in the U.S., and especially to the Three Mile Island nuclear accident. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Kennedy, Richard T., 1919-
Access
Collection is open for research. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org. Collection stored off site; a minimum of two days notice is required for use. Boxes may be requested through Stanford's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1983.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1919 Dec. 24 Born, Rochester, New York
1942-1965 U.S. Army (Colonel)
1959-1961 Planning and financial management adviser to Iran
1962 Army General Staff, Washington, D.C.
1965-1969 International affairs adviser, Office of the Assistant Secretary of Defense
1969-1971 Senior member of the staff, National Security Council
1971-1972 Director, Staff Planning and Coordination, National Security Council
1973-1975 Deputy Assistant to the President for National Security Council planning
1976-1980 Commissioner, Nuclear Regulatory Commission
1981-1982 Undersecretary for Management, State Department
1983- Ambassador-at-large for nuclear non-proliferation affairs
12 Jan. 1998 Died
Scope and Contents note
Speeches, correspondence, memoranda, reports, transcripts of hearings, and printed matter relating to nuclear power plants in the United States, and especially to the Three Mile Island nuclear accident.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
United States. Nuclear Regulatory Commission.; Audiotapes.; Nuclear energy--United States.; Nuclear energy.; Three Mile Island Nuclear Power Plant (Pa.); United States--Politics and government.; Video tapes.
- NUCLEAR REGULATORY COMMISSION OFFICE FILES, 1974-1980. (Box 1-23)
  Scope and Contents note
  Correspondence, memoranda, calendars, telephone logs, extensive background materials for trips and speeches, and a few actual copies of speeches by Richard T. Kennedy. Arranged by form.
- DOMESTIC NUCLEAR REACTOR LICENSING AND REGULATION, 1975-1980. (Box 24-26)
  Memoranda, reports, speeches, letters and miscellany relating to licensing policy and procedure. Arranged by subject.
- INTERNATIONAL REGULATION AND EXPORT LICENSING, 1974-1980 (Box 26-33)
  Speeches, reports, bills, memoranda, letters, hearing transcripts and miscellany relating to non-proliferation issues and to the nuclear activities of various countries. Arranged by country.
- NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION, SAFETY AND RESEARCH, ca. 1967-1980. (Box 34-44)
  Memoranda, reports, letters, speeches, hearing transcripts and operator examinations. Arranged by subject.
- GENERAL THREE MILE ISLAND INVESTIGATIONS, 1979-1980. (Box 45-62)
  Serial issues, telephone logs, reports, hearing transcripts, press releases, speeches, clippings, printed articles, memoranda and letters relating to the accident at Three Mile Island (TMI), Pennsylvania, 1979 March-April. Arranged by originating agency.
- NRC THREE MILE ISLAND INVESTIGATIONS, 1976-1980. (Box 63-88)
  Memoranda, reports, hearing transcripts, speeches, press releases, telegrams, chronologies and letters. Arranged by subject.
- SUBJECT FILE, 1976-1980. (Box 89-90)
  Speeches, memoranda, letters, hearing transcripts, reports and printed articles relating to the economics of nuclear power and alternative energy sources, as well as energy projections and policy issues. Arranged by subject.
- PHONOTAPES
- PHONOTAPE CASSETTES
- PHOTOGRAPHS (Box 10.A-V)
- VIDEOCASSETTES
- RESTRICTED FILE, 1975-1980. (Box 91-92)
  Reports, memoranda and transcripts relating to a variety of issues, arranged chronologically.
- DECLASSIFIED U.S. GOVERNMENT RECORDS, 1976.
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Available as PDF files. The PDF files are page images, so full-text search is not possible. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder by date of creation.
- NUCLEAR REGULATORY COMMISSION OFFICE FILES, 1974-1980
  - General. Primarily NRC administrative issues
    - General. Annual report, pamphlet, regulations and memoranda primarily relating to the Sunshine Act and the Ethics in Government Act, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 1: 1)
    - Conflict of interest, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 1: 2)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 1: 3-5)
  - Calendars
    - 1975-1977 (Box-folder 2: 1-3)
    - 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3: 1-4)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Chronological file. Correspondence and memoranda
    - 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4: 2-3)
    - 1977-1978 June (Box-folder 5: 1-4)
    - 1978 July-1979 June (Box-folder 6: 1-5)
    - 1979 July-1980 April (Box-folder 7: 1-3)
    - 1980 April-July (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Speeches. NOTE: The few copies of speeches by Richard Kennedy are found with related materials under the subsequent entry, "Trips"
    - General. Speeches by other NRC personnel, primarily Commissioners
      - 1975-1976 (Box-folder 8: 2-4)
      - 1977-1980 (Box-folder 9: 1-4)
    - Background materials. Materials for Commissioner Kennedy's speeches, arranged by subject
      - Energy, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 9: 5)
      - International, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 10: 1-3)
      - Non-proliferation and safeguards, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 10: 4-5)
      - Nuclear power, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 10: 6)
      - Nuclear power (contd.) (Box-folder 11: 1)
      - Quotations, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 11: 2)
      - Radiation health effects, 1978 (Box-folder 11: 3)
      - Regulation, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 11: 4)
      - Seabrook (New Hampshire), 1978 (Box-folder 11: 5)
      - States, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 11: 6)
      - Statistics, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 11: 7)
      - Three Mile Island, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11: 8)
      - Waste management, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 11: 9)
  - Telephone logs. Includes attachments of appointment schedules and note pads
    - 1974 Dec.-1975 June 13 (Box-folder 11: 10-11)
    - 1975 June 16-1977 Aug. (Box-folder 12: 1-10)
    - 1977 Sept.-1979 March (Box-folder 13: 1-9)
    - 1979 March-1980 June (Box-folder 14: 1-7)
  - Trips. Includes extensive briefing materials, and a few speeches (See Appendix for details)
    - Draft remarks, 1975 Feb. 24-Sept. 20. Aug. 20 (Box-folder 15: 1-7)
    - (contd.), 1975 Sept. 20 -1976 June 18 (Box 16, Folder 1-10)
    - 1976 Aug. 2-Dec. 16 (Box-folder 17: 1-7)
    - "The NRC and its Regulatory Role,", 1977 Jan. 18-July. 1977 April 20 (Box-folder 18: 1-10)
    - 1977 July 11-Oct. 12 (Box-folder 19: 1-6)
    - 1977 Oct. 13-1978 May 20. (Box-folder 20: 1-7)
      General note
      SEE ALSO: VIDEOCASSETTES for an interview and a presentation given by Commissioner Kennedy in Korea, 1978 March
    - "Cleaning up Our Federal Energy Regulatory Mess," "Health and Safety Aspects of Nuclear Reactor Exports," Remarks, 1978 June 13-1979 Jan. 27. 1978 June 13; Oct. 11; 1979 Jan. 25 (Box-folder 21: 1-9)
    - 1979 Feb. 12-Nov. 13. (Box 22, Folder 1-8)
      SEE ALSO: PHONOTAPES for cassette tapes which include a speech by Richard Kennedy at the American Law Institute-American Bar Association Second Annual Program on Nuclear Export Control, 1979 March; and a reel-to-reel tape of a speech delivered by Richard Kennedy in Madrid, 1979 Nov. 5
    - 1980 March 27-May 6 (Box-folder 23: 1-4)
- DOMESTIC NUCLEAR REACTOR LICENSING AND REGULATION, 1975-1980
  - General. Speeches, letters and responses to Congressional inquiries, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 24: 1-2)
  - Adjudicatory process, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 24: 3-6)
  - Hearing process, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Hearing process (Contd.), 1980 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Immediate Effectiveness Study. Relates to the issue of nuclear power plant construction during adjudication proceedings. Includes several reports
    - Final report, 1978 Feb.-1979 Dec. 1979 Dec. (Box-folder 25: 2-6)
    - (Final report, contd.)-, 1979 Dec. 1980 March (Box-folder 26: 1-2)
  - Lessons Learned. Study Group Recommendations, 1977 April-1979 Feb. (Box-folder 26: 3-6)
- INTERNATIONAL REGULATION AND EXPORT LICENSING, 1974-1980
  - General
    - Export Reorganization Act (S. 1439)
      - 1976 Jan.-March (Box-folder 26: 7)
      - 1976 May-Sept. (Box-folder 27: 1-7)
      - 1980 May-June (Box-folder 27: 8)
    - International Nuclear Fuel Cycle Evaluation (INFCE)
      - General. Speeches and articles, 1978 Feb.-1980 March (Box-folder 28: 1)
      - 1977 Nov.-1979 Aug. (Box-folder 28: 2-6)
      - Licensing, 1976 Aug.-1977 July (Box-folder 28: 7)
    - Non-proliferation and weapons
      - General. Speeches and articles, 1974-1980. (Box-folder 29: 1-5)
        Includes an annual report of the U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency and a presidential report to Congress, 1980 Jan.
      - Conferences. Collections of presentations
        - Japan Atomic Industrial Forum, 1978 March 14-16 (Box-folder 29: 6)
        - International Conference on Regulating Nuclear Energy, 1978 May (Box-folder 29: 7)
        - National Security Affairs Conference, 1978 July 17-19 (Box-folder 30: 1)
        - Atomic Industrial Forum Conference on Nuclear Non-proliferation and Safeguards, 1978 Oct. 24 (Box-folder 30: 2-3)
        - Atomic Industrial Forum Executive Conference on International Nuclear Commerce, 1979 Sept. 11 (Box-folder 30: 4)
        - Organization of American States Conference on the Utilization of Small and Medium Size Power Reactors in Latin America, 1980 May 12-15 (Box-folder 30: 5-7)
  - Great Britain. Reports, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - India. Relates to the export of fuel and components for the Tarapur reactor
    - 1976 Jan.-1978 April (Box-folder 31: 2-6)
    - 1978 May-1979 Oct. (Box-folder 32: 1-8)
    - 1980 Jan.-June (Box-folder 33: 1-3)
  - Soviet Union. DOE "Report of the Visit of the U.S.-U.S.S.R. Coordinating Committee on Scientific and Technical Cooperation in the Field of Thermal Power Plant Heat Rejection Systems to the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics," (DOE/ET-0076), 1978 Nov. (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - West Germany. Relates to the proposed export of reactor components in the construction of a new reactor, 1976 July-1978 Jan. (Box-folder 33: 5-6)
- NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION, SAFETY AND RESEARCH, ca. 1967-1980
  - Emergency Planning
    - 1975 Dec.-1979 June (Box-folder 34: 1-7)
    - Includes comments on an NRC/EPA Task Force report (NUREG-0396), 1979 July-Dec. 1979 Sept. (Box-folder 35: 1-7)
    - Includes materials relating to an organizational discussion, 1979 Dec.-1980 May. 1980 Jan. 8 (Box-folder 36: 1-8)
  - Fuel
    - General, Primarily printed reports (NUREG-0002, NUREG-0290 and NUREG-0095) relating to safeguards and material accounting., 1976 Aug.-1977 May. (Box-folder 37: 1-3)
      SEE ALSO: INTERNATIONAL REGULATION AND EXPORT LICENSING/General/Non-proliferation and weapons
    - American Physical Society Study Group on Nuclear Fuel Cycles and Waste Management report, 1977 March-Oct. (Box-folder 37: 4-6)
  - Information and communications systems. Includes a report by the Mitre Corporation, "Communications and Control to Support Incident Management", 1977 Nov.-1979 Dec. (Box-folder 38: 1-2)
  - Inspection and enforcement. Primarily policy issues
    - Burden of proof in enforcement proceedings, 1976 Oct.-1980 May (Box-folder 38: 3)
    - Civil penalties
      - 1974 Dec.-1979 April (Box-folder 38: 4-7)
      - 1979 May-1980 June (Box-folder 39: 1-2)
  - Operators, 1979 Feb.-Nov. (Box-folder 39: 3-5)
  - Research
    - General
      - General, 1979 April-Nov. (Box-folder 39: 6)
      - Printed reports (NUREG/CR-0147, NUREG/CR-0565, NUREG/CR-0793, NUREG-0577), 1978 June-1979 Oct. (Box-folder 39: 7-8)
    - Anticipated Transient without Scram (ATWS), 1979 Sept.-1980 Feb. (Box-folder 40: 1)
    - Emergency Core Cooling System (ECCS). Report of Advisory Task Force on Power Reactor Emergency Cooling, ca. 1967 (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - Risk assessment
    - General
      - General. Relates largely to the progress of the Risk Assessment Review Group
        - Final report (Lewis Report, NUREG/CR-0400), 1975 Oct.-1979 May. 1978 Sept. (Box-folder 40: 3-6)
        - 1979 July-1980 Feb. (Box-folder 41: 1)
      - Lewis Study. Primarily reaction to and analysis of the Lewis Report
        - 1978 Sept.-1979 Feb. (Box-folder 41: 2-6)
        - 1979 Feb.-July (Box-folder 42: 1-2)
    - Radiation exposure (including occupational exposure), Includes reports by the National Research Council, "Considerations of Health Benefit-Cost Analysis for Activities Involving Ionizing Radiation Exposure and Alternatives," "Occupational Radiation Exposure at Light Water Cooled Power Reactors," (NUREG-0482), and Massachusetts PIRG, "Nuclear Power Plants: Unsafe for Workers,", 1977 Feb.-1979 Sept. 1977; 1979 May; 1979 Aug. (Box-folder 42: 3-6)
  - Siting
    - 1976 Jan.-1977 Dec. (Box-folder 42: 7)
    - 1978 Jan.-1980 Feb. (Box-folder 43: 1-7)
    - 1980 Feb.-April (Box-folder 44: 1-4)
  - Specific reactor sites
    - Clinch River (Tennessee), 1975 April-1978 Aug. (Box-folder 44: 5)
    - North Anna (Virginia). Testimony on licensing (NUREG-0370), 1977 Oct. (Box-folder 44: 6)
  - Terrorism
    - General. Reports, 1976 (Box-folder 44: 7)
    - Anti-Terrorism Act (S. 2236), 1977 Oct.-1978 Sept. (Box-folder 44: 8-9)
- GENERAL THREE MILE ISLAND INVESTIGATIONS, 1979-1980
  - General
    - Articles, 1979 April-Aug. (Box-folder 45: 1-3)
    - Clippings, Predominantly relating to the venting of krypton-85 from the TMI-2 reactor, 1979 April-1980 June. (Box-folder 45: 4)
    - Press releases
      - General, Includes statements by President Jimmy Carter and others, relating to the accident and the subsequent Kemeny Commission investigation, 1979 March-1980 May. (Box-folder 45: 5-6)
      - Associated Press and United Press International, 1979 March-Oct. (Box-folder 45: 7)
    - Telephone transcripts. Incident Response Center
      - General. Miscellaneous sheets to be interfiled with transcripts which are not in this collection (Box-folder 46: 1)
      - Day 5 Channel 19, (April 1, 1979) (Box-folder 46: 2-3)
  - Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI), Nuclear Safety Analysis Center (NSAC), "Analysis of Three Mile Island Unit 2 Accident," Report with indexed bibliography and memoranda comparing this report to NUREG-0600, 1979 July-Oct. (Box-folder 46: 4-7)
  - Energy Department (DOE). Letters and an aerial radiological report, 1979 April-1980 Feb. (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Illinois Commission on Atomic Energy. Report, letter, commission review material, 1979 Oct.-Dec. (Box-folder 47: 2)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc. Serial issue and letters, 1979 Nov. (Box-folder 47: 3)
  - NRC Special Inquiry Group (Rogovin Commission). This was an independent study commissioned by the NRC and prepared under the direction of the law firm of Rogovin, Stern and Huge
    - General. Primarily progress reports and materials related to NRC review of the final report; includes responses to letters from Reps. Toby Moffett and Morris Udall
      - 1979 April-1980 Feb. (Box-folder 47: 4-9)
      - 1980 March-May (Box-folder 48: 1-2)
    - Depositions by Mr. Kennedy, 1979 Oct. 2 (Box-folder 48: 3)
    - Report, (draft), 1980 Jan. 24
      - Parts 1-2 (Box-folder 48: 4-5)
      - Part 3 (Box-folder 49: 1)
  - Pennsylvania, State of. Governor's Commission on Three Mile Island. Report, memorandum and letters, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 49: 2)
  - President's Commission on the Accident (Kemeny Commission)
    - General
      - 1979 April-July (Box-folder 49: 3-5)
      - 1979 July-Oct. (Box-folder 50: 1-2)
    - Depositions
      - Ahearne, John F. (NRC Commissioner), Aug. 29 (Box-folder 50: 3)
      - Bradford, Peter A. (NRC Commissioner), Sept. 10 (Box-folder 50: 4)
      - Denton, Harold (Director, NRC Office of Nuclear Reactor Regulation), May 31 (Box-folder 50: 5)
      - Gallina, Charles O. (NRC Investigation Specialist), Aug. 2 and Aug. 16 (Box-folder 51: 1-2)
      - Gilinsky, Victor (NRC Commissioner), Sept. 8 (Box-folder 51: 3)
      - Hendrie, Joseph M. (NRC Chairman), Sept. 7 (Box-folder 51: 4)
      - Kennedy, Richard T. (NRC Commissioner)
        - General. Background material, including annotated sequence of events and question lists (Box-folder 51: 5)
        - Transcripts
          - 1979 June 1 (Box-folder 52: 1)
          - 1979 Aug. 22 (Box-folder 52: 2)
          - 1979 Sept. 5 (Box-folder 52: 3)
      - Thornburgh, Richard (Gov. of Pennsylvania), Aug. 21 (Box-folder 52: 4)
    - Hearing transcripts
      - 1979 April 25-May 17 (Box-folder 52: 5-8)
      - 1979 May 18-May 31 (Box-folder 53: 1-6)
      - 1979 June 1-Aug. 22 (Box-folder 54: 1-6)
      - (highlighted copy), 1979 Aug. 22 -Aug. 23 (Box-folder 55: 1-2)
    - Reports
      - General
        - General. Background and NRC report review materials
          - Includes "NRC Views and Analysis of the Recommendations of the President's Commission on the Accident at Three Mile Island", 1979 Oct.-Nov. (Box-folder 55: 3-5)
          - 1979 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 56: 1-6)
        - Articles, 1979 Oct.-Nov. (Box-folder 57: 1-4)
      - Final Report and Supplemental Views. Includes index to staff reports (Box-folder 57: 5)
      - Staff reports
        - Office of the General Counsel, "The Nuclear Regulatory Commission" (Box-folder 57: 6)
        - Technical Assessment Task Force
          - "Summary Sequence of Events" (Box-folder 57: 7)
          - "Chemistry" (Box-folder 57: 8)
          - "Thermal Hydraulics"
          - "Core Damage"
          - "WASH-1400--Reactor Safety Study"
          - "Selection, Training, Qualification, and Licensing of Three Mile Island Reactor Operating Personnel" (Box-folder 58: 1)
          - "Pilot-Operated Relief Valve Design and Performance" (Box-folder 58: 2)
          - "Containment: Transport of Radioactivity from the TMI-2 Core to the Environs"
        - Public Health and Safety Task Force (Box-folder 58: 3)
          - "Radiation Health Effects"
          - "Public Health and Epidemiology"
        - Public's Right to Information Task Force. Summary of report only (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - TMI Ad Hoc Nuclear Oversight Committee (Edison Electrical Institute, American Public Power Association, and National Rural Electric Cooperative Association), Report and letters, 1980 March-May (Box-folder 58: 5)
  - U. S. Congress
    - General. Joint House-Senate hearings: Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works, Subcommittee on Nuclear Regulation, Gary Hart, Chairman until 1981, followed by Alan K. Simpson (hereafter referred to as the Hart/Simpson Committee); and House Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Subcommittee on Energy and the Environment, Morris Udall, Chairman (hereafter referred to as the Udall Committee), Transcript and NRC memorandum, 1979 Oct. 31. (Box-folder 58: 6)
    - House of Representatives
      - General
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 58: 7-8)
          - 1979 March-Oct.
          - Includes letter to Rep. Udall in response to inquiry, 1979 Nov.-1980 May. 1979 Nov. (Box-folder 59: 1-2)
        - Legislation (H.R. 2608; H.R. 3415/4174; H.R. 3476; H.R. 4096), 1979 April-Oct. (Box-folder 59: 3)
      - House Committee on Armed Services, Subcommittee on Military Installations and Facilities, Lucien N. Nedzi, Chairman. Memorandum, 1979 May 17 (Box-folder 59: 4)
      - House Committee on Government Operations, Subcommittee on Energy and Natural Resources, Anthony Toby Moffett, Chairman. Includes a hearing summary, a letter from Rogovin, and a transcript of hearings relating to the Rogovin report, 1979 May 14, 1980 Feb. 12, 1980 Feb. 13 (Box-folder 59: 5-6)
      - House Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Subcommittee on Energy and the Environment, (Udall Committee). Includes transcripts, memoranda, and Kennedy responses to questions
        - 1979 May (Box-folder 59: 7-8)
        - 1979 May-Sept. (Box-folder 60: 1-3)
      - House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Subcommittee on Energy and Power, John Dingell, Chairman. Transcript, memoranda and notes, 1979 Nov. (Box-folder 60: 4)
      - House Committee on Science and Technology
        - Subcommittee on Energy Research and Production, Mike McCormack, Chairman. Memoranda and transcripts, 1979 May and Sept. (Box-folder 60: 5-7)
        - Subcommittee on Natural Resources and Environment, Jerome A. Ambro, Chairman. Memoranda, 1979 May (Box-folder 60: 8)
    - Senate
      - General (Box-folder 60: 9)
        - Correspondence, 1979 April-1980 Feb.
        - Legislation (S. 562), 1979 April-May (Box-folder 61: 1)
      - Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works, Subcommittee on Nuclear Regulation (Hart/Simpson Committee).
        - General. Letters from the NRC in response to Committee inquiries, 1979 Oct.-1980 Jan. (Box-folder 61: 2)
        - Hearing transcript, press releases, statement, 1979 April 10. (Box-folder 61: 3-5)
        - Hearing transcript (morning session), statements, memoranda, and responses to questions, 1979 April 23. (Box-folder 61: 6-7)
        - Hearing transcript, statements, and responses to questions, 1979 April 30. (Box-folder 61: 8-9)
        - Kennedy deposition and letters, 1979 Sept. 26. (Box-folder 62: 1)
        - Hearing transcripts, memoranda and statement, 1979 Oct. 2-3. (Box-folder 62: 2-3)
        - Hearing transcripts, letter, memorandum, 1979 Nov. 8-9. (Box-folder 62: 4-5)
      - Senate Committee on Government Operations, Subcommittee on Energy, Nuclear Proliferation and Government Processes, John Glenn, Chairman. Memoranda, transcripts, statements, and responses to questions, 1979 May 8-9 (Box-folder 62: 6-8)
- NRC THREE MILE ISLAND INVESTIGATIONS, 1976-1980
  - General
    - General. Pre-accident materials relating to the operating license, including an inspection report, 1978 Feb.-1980 May (Box-folder 63: 1-4)
    - Correspondence. Incoming. Includes letters and telegrams neither to nor from the NRC
      - 1979 March-April (Box-folder 63: 5-9)
      - 1979 April-1980 July (Box-folder 64: 1-2)
    - Correspondence. Outgoing, 1979 April-1980 Jan. (Box-folder 64: 3-4)
    - Meeting transcripts. Closed meetings
      - 1979 March 30-31 (Box-folder 64: 5-6)
      - 1979 April 1-6 (Box 65: 1-6)
      - 1979 April 9-Nov. 2 (Box-folder 66: 1-9)
    - Meeting transcripts. Open meetings, 1979 April 4-May 17 (Box-folder 67: 1-8)
    - Memoranda. Includes material relating to technical issues and the release of NRC meeting transcripts, 1979 March 29-Aug. 9 (Box-folder 68: 1)
    - Preliminary Event Notification reports, 1979 April 1-Dec. 10 (Box-folder 68: 2)
    - Press conferences, 1979 April 2-May 7 (Box-folder 68: 3-5)